A magical Adventure begins...
Into the West is a adventure, drama, family film directed by Mike Newell.
Accused of a crime they didn't commit, two city kids and a magical horse are
about to become the coolest outlaws ever to ride Into The West.
Papa Reilly, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Kathleen, played by Ellen Barkin.
Ossie, played by Ciarán Fitzgerald.
Tito, played by Rúaidhrí Conroy.
Grandfather, played by David Kelly.
Tracker, played by Johnny Murphy.
Into the West is a 1992 Irish magical realist film about Irish Travellers written by Jim Sheridan
and David Keating, directed by Mike Newell, and stars Gabriel Byrne and Ellen Barkin.
The film explores themes of ireland, stallion, irish.
The tone is emotional.